Henry A. Grunwald Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
Henry A. Grunwald Papers 1922-2006 1950-2004
MSS85225
Grunwald, Henry A. (Henry Anatole)
69,000 items
196 containers plus 1 classified
78.8 linear feet
41 digital files (4.3MB)
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Journalist and diplomat. Personal and professional correspondence, writings, staff files, subject files, and other papers relating to Grunwald's career as a diplomat, author, and editor of Time, inc.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Albright, Madeleine Korbel--Correspondence.; Bernstein, Leonard, 1918-1990--Correspondence.; Brown, Helen Gurley--Correspondence.; Graham, Katharine, 1917-2001--Correspondence.; Grunwald, Henry A. (Henry Anatole); Grunwald, Henry A. (Henry Anatole). One man's America: a journalist's search for the heart of his country. 1997.; Grunwald, Henry A. (Henry Anatole). Saint, more or less: a novel. 2004.; Grunwald, Henry A. (Henry Anatole). Twilight: losing sight, gaining insight. 2012.; Grünwald, Alfred--Correspondence.; Isaacson, Walter--Correspondence.; Kissinger, Henry, 1923-2023--Correspondence.; Maass, Meta, 1911-1987--Correspondence.; Reagan, Nancy, 1921-2016--Correspondence.; Schlesinger, Arthur M., Jr. (Arthur Meier), 1917-2007--Correspondence.
Organizations
American Austrian Foundation--Correspondence.; Council on Foreign Relations--Correspondence.; Time, inc.
Subjects
Diplomatic and consular service, American--Austria.; Journalism--United States.; Vision disorders in old age--Psychological aspects.
Places
Austria--Foreign relations--United States.; United States--Foreign relations--20th century.; United States--Foreign relations--Austria.; United States--History--1945-
Titles
Time.
Occupations
Diplomats.; Journalists.
Acquisition Information
The papers of Henry A. Grunwald, diplomat and journalist, were given to the Library of Congress by his estate from 2005 to 2006.
Transfers
Multiple items have been transferred to the Motion Picture, Broadcasting, and Recorded Sound Division, where they are identified as part of the Henry A. Grunwald Papers.
Related Material
The records of Time, inc. are held by the New—York Historical Society Library and Museum.
Access and Restrictions
The papers of Henry A. Grunwald are open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Manuscript Reading Room prior to visiting. Many collections are stored off-site and advance notice is needed to retrieve these items for research use.
Security Classified Documents
Government regulations control the use of security classified material in this collection. Manuscript Division staff can furnish information concerning access to and use of classified materials.
Digital Format
Digital files were received as part of the papers of Henry A. Grunwald. Reference copies were created from the original digital media. Advanced notice is required for access to digital content; consult reference staff in the Manuscript Division for more information.
Biographical Note
Date Event
1922, Dec. 3 Born, Vienna, Austria
1940 Immigrated to the United States
1944 Graduated, New York University, New York, N.Y.
1945 1951 Foreign correspondent, Time magazine
1951 1966 Senior editor, Time magazine
1953 Married Beverly Suser (died 1981)
1966 1968 Assistant managing editor, Time magazine
1968 1977 Managing editor, Time magazine
1977 Corporate editor, Time, inc.
1978 1987 Editor in chief, Time, inc.
1987 Married Louise Melhado
1987 1990 United States ambassador to Austria
1997 Published One Man's America. New York: Doubleday
1999 Published Twilight. New York: Knopf
2004 Published A Saint, More or Less. New York: Random House
2005, Feb. 26 Died, New York, N.Y.
Scope and Content Note
The papers of Henry A. Grunwald (1922-2005) span the years 1922 to 2006, with the bulk of the material dating from 1950 to 2004. The papers are chiefly in English and are organized into the following series: Family Papers, Correspondence, Writings, Ambassador Files, Time, inc. Editorial Files, and Classified.
Family Papers consist of scattered personal correspondence, printed material, primary school and university papers, and personal documents, some dating from Grunwald's childhood in Austria. Correspondents include his father, Alfred Grünwald, and sister, Meta Maass.
The Correspondence series consists chiefly of personal letters, notes, and emails with individuals and organizations. Items in the Correspondence series are not part of the organizational records of Time, inc. The bulk of the correspondence dates from 1984 to 2004, and is grouped into a chronological file and individual and organization files. There are some letters from family members in the chronological correspondence. Correspondents include Madeleine Albright, Leonard Bernstein, Helen Gurley Brown, Katharine Graham, Walter Isaacson, Henry Kissinger, Nancy Reagan, Arthur M. Schlesinger, Jr., the American Austrian Foundation, and the Council on Foreign Relations.
The Writings series comprises material relating to articles, books, journals, proposed projects, speeches, and student writings authored by Grunwald. Included are articles published in Horizon, Time magazine, and the Wall Street Journal. There is also a significant amount of research material for two autobiographical books, One Man's America and Twilight, and a novel, A Saint, More or Less.
Ambassador Files consist of correspondence, clippings, official documents, and other material from Grunwald's term as United States ambassador to Austria from 1987 to 1990. Included are materials relating to his appointment by President George H. W. Bush.
Time, inc. Editorial Files span the years 1941 to 2005, and document Grunwald's career as managing editor of Time magazine and editor-in-chief of Time, inc. The files consist primarily of photocopies of non-proprietary organizational records held in the Time, inc. Archive, and are organized into the following subseries: Correspondence, Staff Files, Subject Files, and Miscellany. Correspondence is primarily with individuals outside the Time organization, but written in Grunwald’s capacity as a Time, inc. executive and regarding Time publications. Staff Files consist of internal correspondence and memoranda among writers, editors, and general staff. Subject Files include correspondence, notes, clippings, and other materials, concerning events, meetings, groups, organizations, proposed projects, and upcoming articles and publications. The Miscellany series includes calendars and scattered clippings, essays, and speech material.
Arrangement of the Papers
This collection is arranged in six series:
Family Papers, 1922-2000
Correspondence, 1943-2006
Writings, 1940-2004
Ambassador Files, 1983-1995
Time, inc. Editorial Files, 1941-2005
Classified, 1986-1989
Container List
- Family Papers, 1922-2000 (Box 1-3)
  Scattered correspondence, printed material, school papers, and other personal documents concerning Grunwald's family and personal life, some dating from his childhood in Austria.
  Arranged alphabetically by family member or topic.
  - Becoming managing editor of Time, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - Biographical material, undated (Box 1)
  - Birth certificate, Vienna, Austria, 1922 (Box 1)
  - Citizenship papers, 1941-1992 (Box 1)
  - Crusade film project, 1953-1954 (Box 1)
  - Early Time material, 1944-1949, undated (Box 1)
  - Family letters, 1946-1953, undated (Box 1)
  - Freedom of Information Act request, 1975-1990 (Box 1)
  - Grünwald, Alfred (father), 1937-1989 (Box 1)
  - Grunwald family tree, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Heichler, Lucian, 1945-1960 (Box 1)
  - Karlin, Noah, 1947-1965 (Box 2)
  - Maass, Meta (sister), 1946-2000 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous letters and printed material, 1947-1997 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous notes, 1952-1960, undated (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous writings, undated, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Naturalization papers, 1948 (Box 2)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, undated (Box 2)
  - Norton, Joshua, undated (Box 2)
  - Painton, Patricia, 1954-1973 (Box 3)
  - Project proposals, 1948-1956, undated (Box 3)
  - Psychoanalysis, undated (Box 3)
  - Samuel, Rinna, 1948-2005, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - School papers, 1932-1994 (Box 3)
  - Selective Service System, 1947-1990 (Box 3)
  - "Sigmund Freud: Conflict and Culture," exhibit, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C., 1996 (Box 3)
  - Vienna, Austria, 1986-1989, undated (Box 3)
  - Wedding, Beverly Suser, 1953 (Box 3)
  - Wedding, Louise Melhado, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Zwerling, Bruno (Bryan), 1939-1940 (Box 3)
- Correspondence, 1943-2006 (Box 4-26)
  Personal correspondence with individuals and organizations.
  Grouped into a chronological file and individual and organization files, which thereunder are arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent or organization.
  - Chronological
    - 1943-1949 (Box 4)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 4)
    - 1952-1954 (Box 4)
    - 1955-1959 (Box 4)
    - Undated, circa 1950s (Box 4)
    - 1960-1964 (Box 4)
    - 1965-1969 (Box 4)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 4)
    - 1973 (Box 4)
    - 1974 (Box 5)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 5)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 5)
    - 1980 (Box 5)
    - 1981 (Box 5)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 5)
    - 1983-1989 (Box 5)
  - Individuals
    - "A" miscellaneous, 1983-2004 (Box 6)
    - Aab, Bud, 1999-2004 (Box 6)
    - Adler, Mortimer J., 1989-1994 (Box 6)
    - Adler, Stephen, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Albrecht, Thomas, 1990-1994 (Box 6)
    - Albright, Madeleine, 1995-1997 (Box 6)
    - Alexander, Charles, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Allen, Jay, 2003-2004 (Box 6)
    - Angelo, Bonnie, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Arledge, Roone, 2001-2002 (Box 6)
    - Armstrong, Joe, 1994-2001 (Box 6)
    - Astor, Brooke, 1984-1998 (Box 6)
    - Auchincloss, Douglas, 1996-2003 (Box 6)
    - "B" miscellaneous, 1982-2004 (Box 6)
    - Bach, Julian and Hope, 1980-2000 (Box 6)
    - Baker, Howard, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
    - Ballentine, Michael, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Banta, Kenneth, 1988 (Box 6)
    - Barrett, Mary Ellin, 1985-2005 (Box 6)
    - Basch, Peter, 1991-1993 (Box 6)
    - Bass, Anne, 2000-2004 (Box 6)
    - Bastide, Francois-Regis, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Beer, Beatrice, 1999-2000 (Box 6)
    - Begley, Louis and Anka, 1991-2003 (Box 6)
    - Bell, Daniel, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Bell, Virginia, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Bennet, John, 1988-1997 (Box 6)
    - Berlin, Richard, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Bernstein, Leonard, 1988-1989 (Box 6)
    - Bertolini, Gundi, 1993-2004 (Box 6)
    - Bidwell, J. Truman, 2003-2004 (Box 6)
    - Bienstock, John, 1994 (Box 6)
    - Bijou, Rachel, 2004 (Box 6)
    - Billo, Charles, 1991-2002 (Box 7)
    - Biondi, Carol, 2002-2003 (Box 7)
    - Black, Conrad and Barbara, 2000-2003 (Box 7)
    - Blass, Bill, 1999-2000 (Box 7)
    - Bloomberg, Michael, 1997-2004 (Box 7)
    - Blumstein, Susan, 2001-2004 (Box 7)
    - Bodde, William, 1988-1989 (Box 7)
    - Boardman, Cynthia, 2000-2004 (Box 7)
    - Boeth, Margaret "Sissy," 1999 (Box 7)
    - Boorstin, Daniel and Ruth, 1989-2001 (Box 7)
    - Botstein, Leon, 2003 (Box 7)
    - Braddock, Susan, 1999-2004 (Box 7)
    - Bradshaw, Patricia, 1984-1993 (Box 7)
    - Brandon, Muffie, 1993-1996 (Box 7)
    - Brandolini, Simonetta, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Breck, Henry, 1997-2001 (Box 7)
    - Breindel, Joseph, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Brekke, Rosie, 2003 (Box 7)
    - Brenner, Marie, 2000-2004 (Box 7)
    - Brine, Ruth and Kevin, 1982-2004 (Box 7)
    - Brinkley, David, 2003 (Box 7)
    - Bronner, Oscar, 1989-1992 (Box 7)
    - Brooks, Katy, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Brown, Helen Gurley and David, 1988-2004 (Box 7)
    - Brown, Tina, 1996-1999 (Box 7)
    - Buchwald, Ann, 1984-1994 (Box 7)
    - Buckley, William F., 1990-2006 (Box 7)
    - Burbank, Toni, 1987 (Box 7)
    - Burden, Susan, 1998-2004 (Box 7)
    - Burroughs, Polly, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Burt, Richard, 1987-1989 (Box 7)
    - Burton, Sandra, 1988-2000 (Box 7)
    - "C" miscellaneous, 1982-2004 (Box 7)
    - Carter, Graydon, 1998-2004 (Box 7)
    - Cate, Benjamin, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Cave, Ray, 1988-2005 (Box 7)
    - Chambers, David, 2003-2004 (Box 7)
    - Chan, Ronnie C., 1997-1999 (Box 7)
    - Chapin, Schuyler, 1994-2004 (Box 7)
    - Chapman, Bruce, 1989-1990 (Box 7)
    - Chatfield-Taylor, Adele, 1994-1999 (Box 7)
    - Christensen, Henry, 2001-2003 (Box 7)
    - Cisneros, Gustavo and Patty, 1994-2004 (Box 8)
    - Clurman, Richard, 1989-1991 (Box 8)
    - Cogan, Maureen, 1989-1992 (Box 8)
    - Cooper, Matthew and Dan, 1999-2004 (Box 8)
    - Corbin, Richard and Louise, 1991-1997 (Box 8)
    - Corman, Judy, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Crawford, Bruce, 1987-2002 (Box 8)
    - "D" miscellaneous, 1988-2004 (Box 8)
    - Davidson, Ralph and Lou, 1988-2003 (Box 8)
    - Davis, Nick, 2001 (Box 8)
    - De Sabatino, Gabriel, 1993 (Box 8)
    - DeHavilland, Olivia, 1993-2004 (Box 8)
    - Delval, Caroline, 1988-2005, (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Desmond, Ned, 1993-2000 (Box 8)
    - Dewitte, Michael, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Dichand, Hans, 1991 (Box 8)
    - Didion, Joan, 2004 (Box 8)
    - Diebold, John, 1986-1997 (Box 8)
    - Domecq, Jose, 1987-1988 (Box 8)
    - Donovan, Hedley, 1989-1990 (Box 8)
    - Dowd, Maureen, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Dretler, Stephen, 1980-1997 (Box 8)
    - Duchin, Peter, 1992-1999 (Box 8)
    - Duffy, James and Martha, 1988-1997 (Box 8)
    - Dunne, John Gregory, 1992 (Box 8)
    - Durrell, Richard, 1988-1993 (Box 8)
    - "E" miscellaneous, 1987-1999 (Box 8)
    - Eberstadt, Walter and family, 1989-2002 (Box 8)
    - Ecker, Allan, 1987-1997 (Box 8)
    - Eigner, John and Alice, 1988-1992 (Box 8)
    - Eliot, Alexander, 1991-1999 (Box 8)
    - Elliott, Osborne and Inger, 1993-2002 (Box 8)
    - Elizur, Michael, 1988 (Box 8)
    - Eltz, Albert and Katharine, 1991-2003 (Box 8)
    - Ephron, Nora, 1997-2001 (Box 8)
    - Ertegun, Mica and Ahmet, 1990-2002 (Box 9)
    - Evans, Harold, 1987-1999 (Box 9)
    - Evans, Nancy, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Evans, Robert, 1996 (Box 9)
    - "F" miscellaneous, 1987-2004 (Box 9)
    - Fahy, Everett, 1999-2004 (Box 9)
    - Fairchild, John and Jill, 1984-1985 (Box 9)
    - Fairstein, Linda and Justin Feldman, 2002-2004 (Box 9)
    - Feiffer, Jules, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Ferenbaugh, Dorothy, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Ferer, Christy, 2002-2004 (Box 9)
    - Ferguson, Niall, 2004 (Box 9)
    - Firyal, Princess of Jordan, 2002-2003 (Box 9)
    - Flake, Andrew, 1984-1988 (Box 9)
    - Fondaras, Liz, 2004 (Box 9)
    - Foote, Gwyn and Shelby, 1991-1997 (Box 9)
    - Forester, Lynn, 1999-2000 (Box 9)
    - Forster, Brigid, 1998-1999 (Box 9)
    - Foxman, Abraham, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Fritz, Johann, 1990-1994 (Box 9)
    - Fuchs, Michael, 1995-2003 (Box 9)
    - Furstenberg, Georg, 1997 (Box 9)
    - "G" miscellaneous, 1986-2004 (Box 9)
    - Gagern, Riki, 2000-2002 (Box 9)
    - Gaines, Jim, 1991-1995 (Box 9)
    - Galvin, John Thomas and Ruth, 1989-2003 (Box 9)
    - Gardels, Nathan, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Gardner, Edith, 1990-1996 (Box 9)
    - Gates, Henry, 2004-2005 (Box 9)
    - Gay, Catherine, 1987-2001 (Box 9)
    - Gelb, Leslie, 1984-2003 (Box 9)
    - Gibney, Frank, 1993-2000 (Box 9)
    - Gilbert, Gail and Parker, 1997-2003 (Box 9)
    - Gilman, Shirley, 1981 (Box 9)
    - Ginna, Peter, 2004 (Box 9)
    - Ginsberg, Judith, 1999-2001 (Box 9)
    - Goldman, Martin, 1987-1989 (Box 9)
    - Goodale, James, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Goodrich, Henry C., 1989 (Box 9)
    - Gotbaum, Betsy, 2001-2004 (Box 9)
    - Graham, Jean, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Graham, Katharine and family, 1990-2004 (Box 9)
    - Graubard, Stephen, 1993-1999 (Box 9)
    - Graves, Ralph, 1988-2002 (Box 9)
    - Green, Emese, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Greenfield, James, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Greinert, Heldegard and Walter, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Gregg, Gail, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Grierson, Ronald, 2001-2003 (Box 9)
    - Griffith, Thomas, 2002 (Box 9)
    - Grow, Gavin, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Grunwald Park, 1997-1999 (Box 10)
    - Gruson, Marit and Sydney, 1986-1998 (Box 10)
    - Guare, John, 1993-1999 (Box 10)
    - Gunther, Jay, 2000-2003 (Box 10)
    - Gutman, William, 1987-1990 (Box 10)
    - Guyer, David, 1997-2004 (Box 10)
    - Guzzardi, Walter, 1999-2002 (Box 10)
    - "H" miscellaneous, 1983-2004 (Box 10)
    - Haass, Richard, 1996-2004 (Box 10)
    - Haber, Joyce, 1983-1988 (Box 10)
    - Habib, Michael, 1990-1998 (Box 10)
    - Hadley, Leila, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Haller, Roswitha, 1990-2003, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Hamann, Brigitte, 1997 (Box 10)
    - Hampton, Dwaine and Mark, 1986-1999 (Box 10)
    - Hare, Stephen, 1988 (Box 10)
    - Harris, Diane, 1994 (Box 10)
    - Hart, Kitty Carlisle, 1987-1997 (Box 10)
    - Harvey, Sally and family, 1978-1997 (Box 10)
    - Hawkins, Ashton, 1995-2001 (Box 10)
    - Hazzard, Shirley, 1998 (Box 10)
    - Haq, Faisal, 2002 (Box 10)
    - Hearst, Veronica, 1997-1998 (Box 10)
    - Heichler, Lucian, 1987-2005, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Heiskell, Marian, 2003-2004 (Box 10)
    - Henkel, Gabriele and Konrad, 1989-2003 (Box 10)
    - Herrick, Samuel, 1997 (Box 10)
    - Herrera, Carolina, 1994 (Box 10)
    - Herzstein, Robert, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Hohenberg, Prince and Princess of, 1997-2001 (Box 10)
    - Hewitt, Don, 1998-2003 (Box 11)
    - Hickey, Yvonne, 1986-1990 (Box 11)
    - Hill, Britain, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Hoge, James, 1992-2004 (Box 11)
    - Holbrooke, Richard, 1997-2004 (Box 11)
    - Hornik, Richard, 1994-1997 (Box 11)
    - Horvitz, Jane, 2004 (Box 11)
    - Hoxter, Curtis, 1989-1999 (Box 11)
    - Huang, Helen, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Hughes, Robert, 1988-2003 (Box 11)
    - Hunt, Swanee, 1993-1998 (Box 11)
    - Hyland, William G., 1987 (Box 11)
    - "I" miscellaneous, 1989-2002 (Box 11)
    - Ikard, Jayne, 1991-1996 (Box 11)
    - Irving, Florence, 1997-2004 (Box 11)
    - Isaacson, Walter, 1991-2001 (Box 11)
    - "J" miscellaneous, 1987-2004 (Box 11)
    - Jaeger, Maria, 1988-1990 (Box 11)
    - Janklow, Morton and Linda, 1992-2005 (Box 11)
    - Javits, Marian, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Jennings, Peter, 1988-1992 (Box 11)
    - Jerome, Fred, 1991 (Box 11)
    - Joffe, Christine and Josef, 2001-2005 (Box 11)
    - Johns, Margaret, 1999 (Box 11)
    - Johnson, Lady Bird, 2000-2002 (Box 11)
    - Johnson, Lonnie, 1990 (Box 11)
    - Jurich, Marilyn, 2001 (Box 11)
    - Just, Ward, 1997-2003 (Box 11)
    - "K" miscellaneous, 1986-2004 (Box 11)
    - Kahane, Karl, 1991-1993 (Box 11)
    - Kainz, Horst, 1990-2001 (Box 11)
    - Kakutani, Michiko, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Kalb, Bernard and Marvin, 1988-1997 (Box 11)
    - Kalman, Charles and Yvonne, 1984-2004 (Box 12)
    - Kampelman, Max, 1991-1992 (Box 12)
    - Kanfer, Stefan, 1989-2003 (Box 12)
    - Kazin, Alfred, 1994-1996 (Box 12)
    - Kearins, Elizabeth, 2003-2004 (Box 12)
    - Kelly, James, 2000-2003 (Box 12)
    - Kelso, A. Donald, 1997 (Box 12)
    - Kempton, Murray, 1994 (Box 12)
    - Kennan, George F., 1994 (Box 12)
    - Kennedy, Ray and Patricia, 1988 (Box 12)
    - Kerr, Barbara, 2000 (Box 12)
    - Kessler, Frances, 1995-2004 (Box 12)
    - Kilner, Scott, 1990-1991 (Box 12)
    - Kirk, Nancy, 1996-2001 (Box 12)
    - Kirk, Patrick, 1993-1997 (Box 12)
    - Kirkland, Lane, 1988-1999 (Box 12)
    - Kirshbaum, Larry, 1997 (Box 12)
    - Kissinger, Henry, 1988-2004 (Box 12)
    - Klestil, Thomas, 1992-2002 (Box 12)
    - Knight, Andrew, 1988 (Box 12)
    - Koenig, Franz (Cardinal), 1990-2004 (Box 12)
    - Kohl, Helga, 1995-1997 (Box 12)
    - Kollek, Teddy, 1988-2000 (Box 12)
    - Korda, Michael, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Kosinski, Jerzy and Kiki, 1973-2005 (Box 12)
    - Kosner, Edward and Julie Baumgold, 1991-2004 (Box 12)
    - Kotlowitz, Robert, 1994 (Box 12)
    - Kraft, Polly, 1981-1998 (Box 12)
    - Kravis, Henry and Caroline, 1991-2004 (Box 12)
    - Krauthammer, Charles, 1997 (Box 12)
    - Kriss, Ron, 1993 (Box 12)
    - "L" miscellaneous, 1981-2004 (Box 12)
    - Lachs, Thomas, 1998-2001 (Box 12)
    - Lalli, Frank, 1991-1997 (Box 12)
    - Lamm, Herbert, 1991-1992 (Box 12)
    - LaPook, Jonathan, 1997-2004 (Box 12)
    - Larson, Wendy, 2000-2001 (Box 12)
    - Lauder, Jo Carol and Ronald, 1993-2004 (Box 12)
    - Lazar, Irving, 1989-1993 (Box 12)
    - LeClerc, Paul, 1994-2000 (Box 12)
    - Leibenfrost, Luti and Franz, 1990-2004 (Box 12)
    - Lenzhofer, Waltraud, 1993-2004 (Box 12)
    - Leo, John, 2002 (Box 12)
    - Leslie-Melville, Betty, undated (Box 13)
    - Lessing, Traudl, 1985-2003 (Box 13)
    - Levin, Jerry, 1997-1999 (Box 13)
    - Levinson, Bonnie, 1996-1997 (Box 13)
    - Levitas, Mitchel, 1990-2001 (Box 13)
    - Levy, Reynold, 1998-2002 (Box 13)
    - Lewin, Richard, 1997-2004 (Box 13)
    - Lewis, Sarah, 1992-1993 (Box 13)
    - Liberman, Barbara and Robert, 1988-1998 (Box 13)
    - Linowitz, Sol M., 1989-2002 (Box 13)
    - Lish, Gordon, 1991 (Box 13)
    - Loeb, Marshall, 1989-1998 (Box 13)
    - Lord, Shirley, 1994-1997 (Box 13)
    - Lord, Winston and Betty, 1991-1997 (Box 13)
    - Luce, Henry, III, 1980-1998 (Box 13)
    - Luers, William, 1989-2004 (Box 13)
    - Lyons, Josephine, 1997-2004 (Box 13)
    - "M" miscellaneous, 1982-2005, (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Maass, Meta, Walter, and John, 1978-2004 (Box 13)
    - Mader, William, 1994 (Box 13)
    - Maffitt, Peter, 1997 (Box 13)
    - Magnet, Myron, 2001-2005 (Box 13)
    - Malkin, Lawrence, 1992-2004 (Box 13)
    - Mailer, Norman, 1980-1993 (Box 13)
    - Mann, Sivia, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Manning, Robert, 1997-2002 (Box 13)
    - Marbo, Peter, 1998 (Box 13)
    - Marks, Leonard, 1993-1994 (Box 13)
    - Matthews, Thomas S., 1988-1997 (Box 13)
    - Mayhew, Alice E., 1992-2000 (Box 13)
    - McFadden, Cynthia, 1998-2002 (Box 13)
    - McGovern, John H., 1997-1999 (Box 13)
    - McGrath, Tom, 1990-1999 (Box 13)
    - McKinney, Robert, 1996 (Box 13)
    - McManus, Jason, 1987-1994 (Box 13)
    - Medinger, Gregor W., 1988-2001 (Box 13)
    - Meigher, S. Christopher, 1989-1998 (Box 13)
    - Melhado, Christian A., 1986-2003 (Box 14)
    - Merillat, Chris, 1990-1997 (Box 14)
    - Metternich, Franz A., 1990-2003 (Box 14)
    - Mihaly, Lauren, 1987 (Box 14)
    - Millan, William, 2004 (Box 14)
    - Minow, Newton N., 1990-1997 (Box 14)
    - Mitchell, Jennifer and Emily, 2004 (Box 14)
    - Mock, Alois, 1990-1992 (Box 14)
    - Moisi, Dominique, 1997-2004 (Box 14)
    - Molden, Fritz P., 1993 (Box 14)
    - Montebello, Philippe de, 1994-2001 (Box 14)
    - Moody, John, 1992-1995 (Box 14)
    - Moorhead, John, 1993 (Box 14)
    - Morrow, Lance, 1993-2004 (Box 14)
    - Mortimer, Bree, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Mortimer, Siri, 1998-2003 (Box 14)
    - Morton, Frederick, 1989-1996 (Box 14)
    - Mosbacher, Robert A., 1989-1991 (Box 14)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., 1997-2003 (Box 14)
    - Muller, Henry, 1989-1992 (Box 14)
    - Munro, Dick, 1987-1991 (Box 14)
    - "N" miscellaneous, 1984-2003 (Box 14)
    - Nabokov, Dimitri, 1991-1999 (Box 14)
    - Nesbit, Lynn, 1989-2004 (Box 14)
    - Netanyahu, Benjamin, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Newman, Anthony J., 1991 (Box 14)
    - Ney, Edward N., 1989 (Box 14)
    - Nicholas, N.J., Jr., 1989-1999 (Box 14)
    - Nichols, Mike, 1998-2003 (Box 14)
    - Noonan, Peggy, 1998-1999 (Box 14)
    - Nora, Pierre, 1998-1999 (Box 14)
    - Nowotny, Thomas and Eva, 1982-2003 (Box 14)
    - Nozilo, Jerry, 1987 (Box 14)
    - "O" miscellaneous, 1981-2004 (Box 14)
    - O'Connor, Thomas, 1989-2002 (Box 14)
    - Ogden, Christopher, 1991-1997 (Box 14)
    - Olson, Meredith and Jim, 1994-2005 (Box 14)
    - "P" miscellaneous, 1982-2004 (Box 14)
    - Painton, Patricia High, 1967-1997 (Box 14)
    - Pakenham, Michael, 2000-2004 (Box 14)
    - Pakula, Hannah and Alan, 1994-2004 (Box 14)
    - Peabody, Elizabeth, 2002-2004 (Box 14)
    - Pearlstine, Norman, 1996-2005 (Box 14)
    - Pepper, Beverly and William, 1987-1996 (Box 14)
    - Peres, Shimon, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Peters, Elizabeth, 1982-1999 (Box 14)